Works of art
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Works of art
2.1.2.4.21.2
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1391
- Works of art, 2.1.2.4.21.2
  - Holy Family by Sandro Botticelli, circa 1900-1920; 22; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - The Primavera by Sandro Botticelli, circa 1900-1920; 23; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Madonna and Child with St. Sebastian by Antonio da Correggio, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Christ Presented to the People (Ecce Homo) by Antonio da Correggio, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Spring Festival by Eduardo Ettore Forti, 1903; 26; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - In the Time of Nero by Eduardo Ettore Forti, 1905; 27; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - The Starting Line by Edurado Ettore Forti, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - The Damstadt Madonna by Hans Holbein the Younger, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Self-Portrait by Hans Holbein the Younger, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Martin Luther by Hans Holbein the Younger, circa 1900-1920; 31; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - The Knight Errant by Sir John Everett Millais, circa 1900-1920; 32; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Benjamin Disraeli, Earl of Beaconsfield by Sir John Everett Millais, circa 1900-1920; 33; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Hope by George Frederic Watts, circa 1900-1920; 34; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Sir Galahad by George Frederic Watts, circa 1900-1920; 35; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - A Lover of Art by Lawrence Alma-Tadema, circa 1900-1920; 36; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Coronation of the Virgin by Fra Angelico, circa 1900-1920; 37; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  - Self-Portrait by Raphael, Uffizi Gallery, Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 38; 3x4 color (Box 1391)
  Box 1392
- Works of art, 2.1.2.4.21.2
  - Girolamo Savanarola as St. Peter Martyr by Fra Bartolomeo, circa 1900-1920; 1; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Meeting by Marie Bashkirtseff, circa 1900-1920; 2; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Madonna Degli Alberetti by Giovanni Bellini, circa 1900-1920; 3; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Pleasant Hours in the House of Lucullus by Gustave Clarence Rudolphe Boulanger, circa 1900-1920; 4; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Intervention of the Sabine Women by Jacques-Louis David, the Louvre, circa 1900-1920; 5; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Gates of Paradise by Lorenzo Ghiberti, The Baptistry, Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 6; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Bohemian Girl by Fraz Hals, circa 1900-1920; 7; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Cleopatra by Kent[?], circa 1900-1920; 8; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Shoeing by Sir Edwin Henry Landseer, National Gallery, circa 1900-1920; 9; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - St. John and Christ Child by Bartolome Esteban Murrillo, circa 1900-1920; 10; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Four Bulls by Paulus Potter, circa 1900-1920; 11; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - A Strawberry Girl by Sir Joshua Reynolds, National Gallery, London, England, circa 1900-1920; 12; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Elevation of the Cross by Peter Paul Rubens, circa 1900-1920; 13; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Flora by Tiziano Vecelli (Titian), Uffizi Gallery, Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 14; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Self-Portrait by Diego Velasquez, circa 1900-1920; 15; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Princess Mary Stuart and Prince William of Orange by Anthony van Dyck, circa 1900-1920; 16; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - A Chariot Race by Alex Wagner, circa 1900-1920; 17; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Wall painting at casino, Monte Carlo, circa 1900-1920; 18; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Christian Martyrs in Roman Arena, artist unknown, circa 1900-1920; 19; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Kiss of Judas by Ignazio Jacometti, Scala Sancta, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 20; 26; 3x3 color (Box 1392)
  - David by Michelangelo, Accademia Gallery, circa 1900-1920; 21; 755; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Grinder Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 22; 847; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Statue of Apollo, The Vatican Museum, circa 1900-1920; 23; 13598; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Fall of Jericho by Lorenzo Ghiberti, Doors of the Baptistry, Florence, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 24; 3632; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Laocoön and His Sons, The Vatican Museum, Rome, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 25; 3638; 3x4 b&w (Box 1392)
  - The Erba Monument by Santo Saccomanno, Cemetery of Staglieno, Genoa, Italy, circa 1900-1920; 26; 4061; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - The Morning, Palace of the Luxembourg, museum, Paris, France, circa 1900-1920; 27; 15289; 3x4 b&w (Box 1392)
  - Self-Portrait by Joshua Reynolds, circa 1900-1920; 28; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Self-Portrait with Pug Dog by William Hogarth, circa 1900-1920; 29; 3x4 color (Box 1392)
  - Heads of Six of Hogarth’s Servants by William Hogarth, circa 1900-1920; 30; 3x4 color (Box 1392)